Mohamed Sabry Mohamed

Front End Developer

Alexandria, Egypt | abosaadmohamed@gmail.com | +20 128 120 0365 | 22/05/1993 | Egyptian https://mohamed-sabry-portfolio.vercel.app/ | https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamedsabry3/

https://github.com/mohamedsabrie

I am a Front End developer with +1 year of industry experience building websites and web apps. I specialize in JavaScript and have professional experience working with React.js, Next.js, and Tailwind.css. I also have experience working with TypeScript, Redux, Recoil, and Firebase. I like to teach front-end development to others and support them to know how much it is enjoyable to write a code and get a result in front of your eyes

	Education	
2012 - 2018	Bachelor of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, Al-Azhar University	Egypt
	Professional Experience	
06/2021 - present	Front End Developer, AKOIN, Remote At Akoin, I work as a Front End Developer to develop the front end side of Crypto web apps	USA, Remote
11/2021 - present	Front End Developer, Freelance Starting from November 2021 till now I work on a long term real estate project in Saudi Arabia which handle creating contracts with the details between lessors and tenants	KSA, Remote
	Projects in Production	

Projects in Production

MAD DAWGS

Akoin-website

https://www.akoin.io/ 🗹 This is the Akoin website. I was a collaborator working on the home & FAQs & Team pages. we have built it using next.js

Crypterns-website

https://www.crypterns.com/ 🛮 This is the crypterns website. I was a collaborator in this project . we have built it using next.js & Tailwind.css

Skills

HTML/5 CSS/3

JavaScript TypeScript

React.js Redux

Recoil Next.js

Tailwind.css styled-components

Git Github

REST APIS Apollo GraphQL

Jira Agile, Scrum

Firebase Postman API

Material-UI Bootstrap

SASS, SCSS Teaching Programming (Front End Development)

Certificates

 \bullet Web Development Professional Nanodegree from UDACITY $\ensuremath{\square}$

Languages

Arabic • English